all right guys we're doing it we have no
one maybe I didn't click the Twitter
button you didn't click the Twitter
button hello did you click the Twitter
button or no I mean I think it's clicked
by default
I don't know broken why is this printing
up about if you didn't follow is
this on Twitter Bros oh yeah we've 38
just turn it on it takes a little bit of
time no notification spot okay okay okay
so maybe we're good notifications it's
good they just saw just said
notification squad notification squad
yeah you hit that subscribe button to
get access and notice gang is this on
Twitter you guys see five it must be a
lot of people have signed up all right
guys it's terrible you getting that for
yo did you talk to these people don't
sleep whoa yeah I don't sleep your heart
do his work work work no matter what I
got on Twitter cool it's on Twitter
that's something right cool
oh yeah so guys we are going to buy a
car
who knows what we're buying people know
I know yeah didn't know what those are
mounts for Dooley on technology that's
right we can't even go to quality on
Tripoli on technology go crazy yeah I'm
taking lemon lime Gatorade this scope is
brought to you by lemon I'm Gatorade
okay if you want to sponsor me we don't
have to do hashtag ad if we should show
four things because we like them it's
not a hashtag had no but we should look
okay but once Gatorade pays us we're
gonna let you know I will sorry Gatorade
night George ate the perfect amount from
Panda Express sponsorship that'd be fine
yo I actually got contacted by a guy who
knows an executive at Panda Express
really yeah oh I knew this Panda well
yes we have a big guy we were big
announcement coming about panda pretty
soon you know we're moving into new
methods of online distribution you guys
can probably guess but we are looking
for an exclusive IRL distributor of the
common type an and we think that Panda
Express would be perfect
yeah so if we could like get it in like
to Panda Express stores you know maybe
like we'll give them each free ten
pandas
alright I'm making like so much a
restaurant Panda Express of course
okay that's why it's funny oh that's why
cuz like partnerships are dumb as
but like that's humorous right scheme
and we can put out like an official
press release about how come AI is
partnering with Panda exactly would you
like an e on with your meal they got it
yeah right it's a happy meal exactly
it's like Pizza Hut and it's like
dominoes and for teaming up on
self-driving yeah that's the thing is
people take that seriously right like
hopefully that'll trigger something in a
few people's minds yeah I see expresses
you mean the like the shooter chicken
place yeah sugar chicken place why you
don't think oh yeah I just got mine
there yeah we have a lot of snow peas we
have a hundred scope we loaded scope
these guys we're going to buy a car big
we're going to the Ford dealership Bros
that's what we should do market research
for we should hire someone for that by
the way this is one HDR and it's banner
I fixed a bug in HDR last night too I
found like one last little bug and it
makes just the quality like little salty
how nice is that long
you guys all the pasta I'm getting
really good we're gone for us whoo that
was definitely illegal right like that's
the thing like I was judging that like a
very normal speed puff puff don't slow
yet hi so we're going to car dealership
now we got a cutout up here
this is a it's a diffusion problem it's
never been an issue before no that's
always an issue when you're coming up on
a stopped car it fuses but it fuses late
it's uncomfortable breaker yeah but it
will fuse like it'll give you time and
if you but yes stop cars are I mean
there's you know autopilot is the same
problem there's a few word to infuse
does this like footage on your grandma's
cars nice no really I love the red core
here we have the rav4 is my favorite car
but we were about to go buy a Ford
Fusion we'll go on a Ford dealership do
you know what exit we get off to the
Ford dealership yep I should know
dealerships all the time there's ones
closer than this one's close to the
melody of Ricardo when I went there okay
so you guys know that uh
I don't really like Ford so uh yeah well
exactly like what if someone's in the
dealership watching we're kind of like
infiltrating Ford well okay so we showed
up to this dealership once and we asked
if we could plug in a panda just sniff
the canvas on the car and the guy like
like looked at us and they're like we
hate you I'm about like Big Dave like
really hated us like I'm not even
exaggerating Ford
Dana speak it uses
so that's what I'm saying like wherever
the Honda one is is the same place
return car put in the more acceleration
of accelerate except they're often the
acceleration on all the cars the the
exodus can't like them you can tell them
47 that if any scope is want to come I
know she ate hard yeah why by Ford if
people already working on for people
already working on the pork uh because
the data speak in a lot of the other
self-driving car companies are using
this as a base platform and we want to
make sure that we are at least a
superset of them right all right Sara
Monte right we want to make sure that
we're a superset of the other self every
car companies he really tries better
with HDR I haven't like yeah it feels
really good it feels good
here's like yeah you don't even like
think about on file anymore because okay
so we have you know big things coming
this year it's getting so easy for us to
park cars yeah
I'm wait
is there going to be official port for
form tasks what he presently doing
I think there will be I think we're
actually gonna remove the bounty and
to improve current lighters
why aren't I have a long Skokie last
night where we talk about line I rap for
the scope is tough
what yeah we're down
you got his cookies
yeah people are really excited to
present like shown in the wheel totally
showing off all the pilots are we Brian
are we buying a hybrid plasm we are
buying the nicest watch already got I
don't know I don't know Eddie got a
Volvo and you never showed me his car
yeah it's an old Volvo it's really
pretty but it's it's old salt
it's dangerous bro it's super dangerous
for trees and safe they better be Connie
produced um whoa yo I would settle for
like like hot sugar the guy you used to
produce for kitty pryde to produce a Tom
Cruise nevermind Kanye you got to start
small man not sugar if you're out of
tannin kutsher's Kenny price producer
and then she ended up dating him really
true story okay project Oh Paul Paul
those are awesome love it you should
talk to many about that he doesn't oh
yeah he's stoked on it
when they can see the wheel look at this
it looks right on this screen but it's
actually very nice no I think that's uh
yeah of course
alright welcome to sur Oh Monty for yes
Monty Ford where the Sun never shines
but the people always smile do they
smile cerimon before yeah going down
here prepare Oh what is this oh this is
the tiny parking lot at Sarah Monty Ford
where you can never fall there's no
parking I'm not breaking the rules
already no no it said no part but I
think it's a no remember that's how I
got banned from Tesla well the time
we've bought a Tesla and then we got a
call the next day and they're like you
don't get a Tesla we put the incorrect
type you really should have bet on the
Model X too expensive we didn't have
that much money back then but now Oh
Eddie we're not to see your car no all
right we're gonna bring moving this
gobies to the door no fees we're gonna
bring you in on that on the DL okay sure
they were shootin
watch the truck and I will bring him to
the door we will respect the guys
because look have a look at me with a
head look guys it's all about some
respect
just saying I respect you I respect
[Laughter]
arting overlap yeah does it no look at
that my gaiter is gonna be warm we go
back to the car yeah bring it in it like
shows a sense of like authority that
you're walking in with you know the
Gatorade yeah where did I walk into with
stuff go you just walk at Nobu with no
shoes this is intense
does that even know
please keep stoking it's gonna be
low-key nice you really need one of
those things that you hold and it like
stabilizes your phone I don't know
what's asking service in parts do I need
them I didn't really do Scorpius it was
nice next time you see me I'm gonna wait
you left already
no we're still there you know yep yeah
oh yeah
next time you see me would be the pad
owning uh-huh a fusion hybrid and I'm
guys make sure to hit that like and
subscribe button you know make sure come
in and check out that comment that AI
slash shop go go buy things ships today
if you buy visible fulfill it